A Guide to the Student Wives Club, 1961-1977
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
A Guide to the Student Wives Club 1961-1977
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
37-2A
1 Hollinger box and 3 scrapbooks
Student Wives Club
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Open to researchers without restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Given to the Archives by Campus Security on May 17, 1984.
Scope and Content
Materials include correspondence, financial records, meeting minutes, scrapbooks, and other items related to the business of the organization. Materials date from the 1960s and 1970s.
Index Terms
College students' spouses; Correspondence; Financial records; Administrative records; Scrapbooks
Contents List
- Correspondence (Box-folder 1:1)
- Financial Records (Box-folder 1:2)
- Minutes May 1961-April 1964 (Box-folder 1:3)
- Minutes September 1964-May 1965 (Box-folder 1:4)
- Minutes August 1965-May 1966 (Box-folder 1:5)
- Minutes September 1966-May 1967 (Box-folder 1:6)
- Minutes September 1967-May 1968 (Box-folder 1:7)
- Minutes July 1968 (Box-folder 1:8)
- Minutes September 1970-May 1972 (Box-folder 1:9)
- Minutes September 1972-April 1975 (Box-folder 1:10)
- Minutes June 1975-March 1977 (Box-folder 1:11)
- Miscellaneous (Box-folder 1:12)
- P.H.T. Degrees (Box-folder 1:13)
- Print-outs (Box-folder 1:14)
- Space Reservation Requests (Box-folder 1:15)
- Standing Rules (Box-folder 1:16)
- 1961-1969 (Volume Scrapbook 1)
- 1969-1975 (Volume Scrapbook 2)
- 1975 (Volume Scrapbook 3)